Thank you for watching!
Here you go! It's starting!
It's time for the "Halo"! This time I'm joined by Yume Kudo from Juice- Juice and Marin Fukuda from Tsubaki Factory.
This time, we'll be presenting you with these two, so please bear with us until the end.
Today, February 21, the day of distribution, is the release date of Tsubaki Factory's new album, 3rd Moment.
Congratulations!
For me, this is my first album since joining Tsubaki Factory,
I myself bought Tsubaki Factory's 1st Bloom and 2nd Step myself,
I myself bought Tsubaki Factory's 1st Bloom and 2nd Step on my own, so it's a strange feeling to have my voice on an album that I have such an emotional attachment to,
I am very happy to have my voice in such an album that I have such a strong attachment to.
Do you have a favorite song?
Well, I am very attached to the song "Power Flower," which is a new song on Disc 2 of the album,
This song is very powerful and has Tsubaki Factory's style in it,
Especially, there are many rap parts in this song, and the three of us are doing the rap parts,
There are many rap parts in this song, and I am very happy to be chosen as one of the three members to do the rap part,
I will do my best to make it cool.
I will do my best to make it cool. I'd like to do my best to be cool.
Yes, I have been working with the new members of Tsubaki Factory for a couple of times,
I have worked with the new members of Tsubaki Factory a couple of times, and I was impressed by how young all three of them are.
We are in the second and third year of junior high school, so our ages are quite far apart,
We are the same age, 19 years old.
Junior high school students, huh?
I think it's cute that they all seem to be having fun talking about school,
I think all three of us are very soft, yet have a core,
I am very happy to have these girls who are so typical of Tsubaki Factory,
For me, it's the first time to be a junior member, so I'm very anxious about it,
I'm very anxious about it, but if you have any advice on how to treat junior members, please let me know.
Well, I think there are a lot of things we don't know about each other,
I think there are a lot of things we don't know about each other, so I would like to communicate with them a lot first,
I really liked origami, so I thought I could play with it in my free time at work,
I had an origami set and asked them to play with it with me.
I would love to know if you have any hobbies or interests,
I'd love to hear about your hobbies and interests, but I'm interested in what you have to say.
I look forward to hearing from you.
So, without further ado, please take a look at this video.
Here it is!
Let's start filming right away!
It's early, it's early, it's early!
Everybody put your hands up!
That's the signal to get started.
A shining story, a fawning foley
The city in red blooms, rigid and motionless
The city in red, the city in red, the city in red, the city in red, the city in red, the city in red
Youth go! First, lilance
Youth shukyo, if you know what I'm talking about
Ride on those eyes, jump on that noise
Jiri jiri bye bye game show time
Engine Blow!
Everything's gonna be alright
Tsubaki, hanabi, hanabi, I swear everything's alright
The power that overlaps is toward the blue sky
The figure is dignified, graceful, and beautiful
A dream I want to make bloom all over the world
I can't make it come true on my own
Redder and redder, you who keep on shining
That word
Now is the time to come together as one
We'll soar with our hearts in unison
To a heart you've never seen
Wow, wow, wow, wow
Now is the time to come together
♪ Now is the time to soar together
To hearts you've never seen
Wow, wow, wow, wow
Everybody put ur hands up
Move ur body
Movement starts with 1.2.3
Teppo poppo and meeting is a coincidence
Crouching down transmission
Curiosity rather than fear Voice
The turn in the key of sex is a movie
Painting tomorrow with determination determination
A life that won't be dented by a little
Take it out Destination is make-up
It's in the freezing winter
Sleeping needles, waiting for spring
What shines beyond the long thaw
Trust in the heat
The voice I want to echo around the world
For you
Don't think with your head, catch it in your heart
Loudly, loudly, loudly, make it bloom in all its glory
The dream I want to make bloom all over the world
I can't make it come true alone
Red, redder, redder, you who keeps on illuminating
That thing
Now is the time to unite as one
My way
To a place I've never seen before
Wow wow wow wow
Now is the time to come together
My way
To places you've never seen
Wow wow wow wow
Everybody put your hands up
Don't you want it? Let's try to put your hands up.
Yume Kudo of Juice-Juice and Marin Fukuda of
and Marin Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory present "Halo! stay!
From here, I'd like to talk a little about each other.
I'm going to ask you a question first, so don't think too much and answer at a quick pace.
Marin-chan says her hobby is eating.
What is your favorite food right now?
Hot pot.
What is something surprising about your short cut that you didn't notice before you started wearing it two months ago?
I have a hard time with my sleeping habit.
Your new album "3rd Moment" was released today.
If you were to give Marin a catchphrase, what would it be?
Shin-tsubaki.
Marin has an image of studying hard.
What do you like to study with?
Something sweet.
It was announced that Shinnuma-san, the leader of the group, would be graduating.
What do you want to learn from her until then?
Tsubaki-ness.
Thank you very much.
How do you like the short cut?
I didn't get a chance to take a good look at it after I wore it short
I'm glad I'm sitting here now.
Is it hard to sleep with?
It's very difficult, because when I have shorter hair than when I have longer hair, the ends of my hair get caught in pillows and things like that.
I see.
It gets all wavy and explodes in the morning.
I didn't realize that until it got a little shorter.
It's hard to get rid of it in bed.
I'll do my best.
When it was announced that Shinnuma-san would be graduating, you mentioned something about the character of Tsubaki.
Do you have any specifics?
Shinnuma-san is an original member of Tsubaki Factory
I think that you are the person who knows best what Tsubaki Factory is like.
Recently, Tsubaki Factory has been increasing its repertoire of songs.
Of course there are some ephemeral songs, but there are also more and more cool songs.
There are of course ephemeral songs, but there are also more and more cool songs.
But the fragility of the music is also something I really value.
I hope I can learn a lot from you while you are here.
I also hope to see a lot of it.
Questions for Mr. Kudo after the VTR
Hello! Ste. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11
Shall we dance?
Shall we dance? Is it because of the summer?
Wacky wacky wacky wacky wacky wacky wacky wacky wacky wacky wacky wacky wacky wacky tea horse!
Ocha no Ma! First album Channel 1 now on sale!
Hallo! Ste!
Next, I would like to ask you a question, Mr. Kudo!
Yes, I'm looking forward to it!
Speaking of octopus, what is your favorite octopus these days?
I'm addicted to octopuses that have a shell called an octopus boat.
How would you like to enjoy your teenage years to the fullest in the next six months?
Speaking of 10, there is a tribe of octopuses called the 10-letter octopus tribe.
I would like to learn more about it!
Hello Project 2024 Winter 3overse is currently underway.
What do you want to express through this tour?
I would like to increase the number of picturesque expressions.
What do you do for your powerful dance?
I started core training last year.
What do you want to do with the juice juice in your current position?
Well, first of all, I would like to do a live concert with all 11 of us.
I would also like to add to my collection of memorable photos.
That's wonderful.
Thank you very much.
I was wondering, how do you want to enjoy your teenage years?
You mentioned octopus.
When I hear the number 10, I think of the 10-letter octopus tribe.
Yes, there is such a thing as a 10-letter octopus.
There are also octopuses with 10 letters, but there are also octopuses with 10 letters and octopuses with 10 letters.
The 10-letter octopus is an octopus that lives in the deep sea.
When I heard "10," I thought I had to study it.
There are about 10 different kinds of octopuses.
I know about them, but I don't know much about them.
I'd like to learn about them.
Please let me know when you learn more.
Thank you very much.
I would like to ask you about your powerful dance and what you are striving for in your dance. What do you do for your dancing?
Well, last January.
I've been doing core training for about a year or so.
I've been doing core training for a little over a year, about 9 minutes a day, which is really not much time.
But thanks to that, I thought my balance had improved a little bit.
I am very happy to hear that you like my powerful dancing.
I always think your dance is so cool.
I'd like to start core training too.
More to come! Stay tuned for more after this!
This is Masashi Natsuyaki.
This is Riho Utano from Beyond Seasonings.
I'm going to try my best to make sweets again this week.
What would you like to make this time?
I would like to make a chiffon cake.
What about this kind of cake?
I have never made cakes before.
I see. Well then, let's do our best for today's challenge.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm nervous.
It's getting mixed up.
I cracked up a little.
It's okay if it's cracked. It's the right thing to do.
It's good.
Last time you baked the dough in the oven, but where do you start this time?
Chiffon cake is plain, so you want it to be a little prettier.
I've prepared strawberries, which are in season right now.
Let's make it pretty.
Since we're going to go through the trouble, I'd like to try cutting up three kinds of decorations.
First, hearts.
Listen to me, how to say it nicely.
Cut it in half.
Cut the head into parts,
Round the perimeter just right.
This seems to be the important part.
If you cut it and tell it to be pretty, it will be pretty.
Be cute.
I'm really asking you.
What do you think?
It's a little prettier.
It's good, isn't it?
It's a heart.
I'm nervous.
It looks more difficult than it looks.
Smile.
It's difficult. I knew it.
It looks difficult.
Here is the first one.
Doesn't it look like a heart to you?
It's more like a song.
It's really bad.
This one is cuter.
I wonder why.
And so it went.
It's just baked,
I'll look at the cake first.
Let's see.
You're going to take it, right?
Yes. Be careful.
Oh!
It smells so good.
I have to shock you again,
Hold this from the side,
And then pop it down.
A little higher. Drop it from this level.
Then, I drop it again.
Pop it again and let go.
Are you sure?
On!
On.
It's OK.
Ah! OH!
Good balance.
It's done with exquisite balance.
Just the way it is?
Here we go. Here we go.
I didn't do anything.
It's okay.
I'm okay.
I think I'll be fine.
Okay, back to the strawberry showdown.
This way?
Strawberry. I'll cut strawberries.
I want to go back to the strawberry showdown.
I think I might have found it.
I think the teacher might have noticed something.
It might be a good showdown.
Here we are.
What do you think?
It's good, right?
Hart.
It's good.
Heart?
Bad?
Yes.
Then I'll have this one.
Soft strawberries on the outside.
No good.
Like rabbits.
Like cherry blossom season.
It's gentle.
So, this is the match.
The first round,
It became a heta job.
It looks like there are still two more rounds.
This time, we will drop the heta and use one of them.
Make a cut,
Cut a slit in the bottom and stop it at the bottom.
Cut it off and take it out.
It looks difficult.
Wow!
That's great.
Beautiful.
Good.
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
You can't spread it out unless you're on the edge, right?
It's kind of sinking a little bit, but I got one.
But..,
Will it work?
This is the hard part.
It might be difficult.
It's okay.
It's done.
It'll be back to one in about 10 minutes.
Yup.
It's going to be back.
You cut too much, doctor.
This is a good match.
This is because the teacher cut it off,
This might be a draw.
That's not true.
I often do this with eggs and cucumbers at the end.
Cut it in,
I cut a little bit off.
He put it down.
Cute.
It's cute.
It comes in all shapes and sizes.
Wow!
Stick it right in the middle,
Just a little bit.
I've seen it before, but I've never done it.
It is surprisingly easy to do,
It looks difficult, but it's not so difficult when you do it,
But when you do it, it's not so difficult.
It's not so difficult when you do it.
Losing track is the right answer.
Don't you lose track?
I don't know again.
This is a little confusing, isn't it?
Yes, they are.
It's so beautiful.
So beautiful.
Victory!
Winner!
It's so beautiful.
He's so good.
I'm a little surprised. Now.
I'm here.
Amazing!
I'm a little surprised. Now.
This is good.
I could do it.
I'll make it a special skill.
That's great.
You have a new skill.
Yes.
Next time
Next time, let's use whipped cream.
Speaking of strawberries, fresh cream is the best.
Let's add all the cream and miyabushi juice.
Do you like it? I love it.
Now, here's a point for you.
Put all the sugar in first. That's right.
There is a way to put it in in the middle,
But if you put it in halfway, the sugar will dissolve,
The granulated sugar will not dissolve and will leave a rough texture,
Granulated sugar may not dissolve and may leave a coarse residue, so put it all in at the beginning.
In this case, we will add 15 grams.
Put it in right away.
How far into the mixture should this be?
I think you can put it in until it is about the size of a cube.
It's the same as meringue.
Does it fall off?
This pattern is like a cril.
Put the cream in the refrigerator.
Now all that's left is that.
I've been waiting for a long time.
Keep it turned over.
Let's cut it with a knife.
I put it in all the way to the back, and I can turn it this way.
Put it in like this,
Turn it this way,
Do the same for the outside.
This time, I want it to be on the outside.
Like dough.
If you do it all at once, it will fall apart.
Like this.
It looks good.
It's so beautiful.
It's totally fine.
It's more like you're turning it around again with the image of hitting the bottom.
It will be fine as long as it cools down.
It's still warm and soft today, so it's difficult to do.
But it's totally fine.
Ready, set, go!
It's done.
Beautiful! Beautiful!
It looks great.
It can be cut very nicely.
A good size.
Cut the size you want to eat,
You can eat it later.
You will be diagnosed, you know.
Diagnosis.
How much do you want to eat?
Let's go with a big one.
Are you sure?
How much do you want to eat?
I think it's pretty.
It's so beautiful.
Soft and fluffy.
Looks delicious.
Is this the side?
It's this kind of place, isn't it?
But it looks so cute.
Here we go. Ready.
Momentum is the key.
I want to put this on.
It's already perfect.
Reversed munchies.
This is cute.
Beautiful.
Sponge cake is ready.
The chiffon cake is ready.
So, how do you like it, Tano?
I'm not good at baked goods that usually require an oven,
I was surprised to see how beautiful and fluffy it turned out.
It's amazing.
It really turned out beautifully.
Now, please try it.
Yes, I will. Bon appétit.
Bon appétit.
Yum!
Delicious!
The sesame oil flavor is still there,
It's very savory.
It's good.
It smells like manera,
Leftovers? Manera?
Yes. They're both still there.
That's good. Well, I look forward to seeing you again at Hello Kitchen.
So, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now, Hello Kitchen.
Yume Yakami of Juice- Juice and Mari Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory present "Hello! STE.
From here on, we'll be talking about the Hello! Project Chotto No. 1!
Project Chokotto No.1! Project, we conducted a survey on a little bit of a theme.
We will announce who is the No.1 in a ranking format.
The theme this time is which member I want to be a big sister.
By the way, Mari, who do you think would be No.1?
I think Morning Musume。's Akemi Haga, who I voted for. I personally think it will be Akemi Haga of Morning Musume's 24, whom I voted for.
When I talk with her, I feel a sense of security, and she makes me feel very warm and fuzzy.
I think that's why she is in the ranking.
By the way, I voted for Shin Maeda of Beyonce,
Ms. Maeda has a very calm atmosphere, and she talks to me a lot, Tako-chan,
I voted for her because I have a personal wish that she would be my big sister.
Let's take a look at the ranking!
The three members were in a tie, so I'll announce the names first.
The third member we would like to see as a big sister is Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 24's Ayumi Ishida, who received 5 votes,
The third place went to Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 24's Rena Yokoyama and Ayano Kawamura of Angulum.
The members who voted for Ms. Ishida are as follows,
She is kind, funny, and sincere, so I think it would be great if she were my sister.
Eishion Tamura said, "She is kind, funny, sincere, and I think it would be great if she were my big sister.
The other comment was from Ruru Tamura, who is caring, kind, strong, and cool.
That's right.
The comment for Yokoyama-san was from Homaru Okamura, who simply makes you feel like she is your big sister.
Honoka Kobayashi's comment to Ms. Kawamura was, "I want her to be like a friend, but a dependable big sister.
The comment for Ms. Kawamura came from Ms. Rena Yokoyama, who said that she admires Ms. Kawamura in many ways: she is firm but also very cute.
Shiori Yaguchi, who I think is very kind, versatile, and wonderful, and has a little bit of a gap between herself and her sister, who I think is very interesting.
Kawamura-san, I often go out with you, and you really are like an older sister.
Yes, she is.
I'm really like an older sister. Ste!
Next up, we have comments from the members who voted for the second place! I often feel like an older sister when I'm with her.
One commenter, Elisa, said that she would be happy if she were actually her big sister. She is kind and always pampers me, arranges my hair for me at concerts, and is very kind to me.
I had a hunch that it would be her, but I was surprised to find out that she was the one I wanted to be the big sister of the group.
The second member I would like to see as a big sister is Danbaralulu from Juice Chusu, who received 7 votes!
I, Kudo, think that Ms. Damballa and her sister and big sister of Juice Chus have warmth like a mother, but I also think that Ms. Damballa is very good at arranging hair and she is also very good at arranging hair.
I am so grateful to her for arranging my hair, and for her relaxed attitude.
I think she is a very reliable sister of Juice Chus. The first place was announced after the VTR.
Shake it out, Shake it out, Shake it out!
Shakein' it up! Shakein' it up!
Oh, no... Again...
A little mistake and that kind of temper... and you're down.
It happens all the time.
You'll wake up, Cheapalet 321.
Yeah, I know, right?
A dream I haven't even told my parents about yet.
Bigger and bigger. Much, much freer.
It's okay, if it's with you
Shake it up, the future that no one knows
Our future will open up with our own hands
Just hop! step! Shake it up!
Just hop, step, Shake it up, Jump!
Shake it up Power to believe in yourself
Ordinary, but you're honest
Here comes my chance
Darling up and down
Shake it up
Shake it up No hard feelings
Shake it up Shake it up
Bouncing words are my cue
Feelings reaching more and more
If it's something you shouldn't forget
Say Happy Lucky if you're finishing up
The future that no one knows
Our hands will open the door to the future that no one knows
Let's just keep dancing and do it
Shake it up!
The power to believe in freedom
I'm ordinary, but I'm sharp
I've got a chance to do the same
Turn it up and dance!
I wanna feel it, I wanna feel the love
I want it!
I wanna feel the love
I wanna feel it, I wanna feel the love
I wanna feel your love
And I wanna love you
Woo Woo
Sing it!
Thank you for your hard work!
Yume Yakami of Juice- Juice and Marin Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory present "Halo! Sta.
We are going to introduce a little theme for all the members of the Hello! Project, we have conducted a survey on a small theme and announced who is the number one member of the project in the form of a ranking.
The theme of this year's survey was "Which member would you like to be your big sister? The third place was tied between Ayami Ishida, Rena Yokoyama, and Ayano Kawamura, and the second place went to Ruru Danbara.
The first question was, "Which member would you like to be your big sister? Who is the first place winner? Please watch the VTR. Please watch the VTR.
Yes, because she was the first person that came to mind when I was asked who I would like to be my big sister, and also because she is always kind to me and takes care of me.
Just by looking at her, I thought, "What a beautiful woman! How beautiful she is! If she were my sister, I would be so proud of her. There are so many things that I admire about her that I would want to be a member of her sisterhood.
First of all, my first impression of her was that she was very beautiful and radiated an overwhelming aura, so when I talked to her, I wondered if it was okay for me to talk to her or not. But when I talk to her, she gives me a fluffy impression, has a wonderful smile, and is a little bit out of the ordinary, which I think is really wonderful,
If she becomes my big sister, I will be proud of her for the rest of my life.
The member I would like to have as my big sister is Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice.
I am Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice.
You have chosen me as the No. 1 member you want to be your big sister.
Then, No.1!
So, I have the impression that I'm quite surprising.
I am an only child.
I have a strong yearning for older sisters, older brothers, younger sisters, and younger brothers.
So I was happy to hear you say that.
When I heard this, I thought to myself, "This is what being a big sister is all about.
I carry a blotting sheet with me.
When I carry a blotting sheet, the members who are not me
When I carry a stain-removing sheet, the members who are not me don't spill food on it.
or a pen got a little stain on it...
"Mr. Kamimura!
Mr. Kamimura, I'll give you a blotting sheet.
"I have some, I have some...
I always get calls saying, "Oh, you're always so helpful!
I always have a stain remover sheet and other things in my bag.
That's the secret of being a big sister.
But I still think that the ideal big sister is...
I'm drawn to older sisters, or older sisters.
That's what I'm drawn to.
My ideal older sister is someone who has a sense of intimacy with me.
I'd like to get closer to that ideal.
I think I'm pretty much like this at the moment.
The questionnaire made me sound like a fluffy older sister, so...
I'm not like that.
I'd like to be a leader who pulls people along.
She's not a leader, she's a big sister.
The leader is the leader of JuiceJuice.
I'm going to do my best to be a mature older sister.
Oh, I'm going to spill it again! It's almost gone!
You're down, that's good!
Pull yourself together already, really. I won't forgive you next time.
It was Mr. Uemura, wasn't it?
She is in the same group as me, JuiceJuice,
She's a member of the same group as me, JuiceJuice, and she's very friendly and a very senior member of the group,
He told me that he brought this dress because he thought it would look good on Taco,
I often received hand-me-downs from them,
I was also very surprised to hear that I was ranked No. 1.
When I heard that you were ranked No. 1, I thought, "That makes sense,
I often watch your performances from the stage count,
I can understand why you would want to show off your sister to all kinds of people if she were your big sister.
Hello! Project Chokonto No. 1, please look forward to the next issue.
Hello! Project Chokotte No.1, look forward to the next installment.
Yume Kudo of Juice- Juice and Marin Fukuda of Tsubaki Factory present "Halo! STE. It's time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
Project 2024 Winter 3 of Us will be held in the middle of the year. Project 2024 Winter 3 of Us is now underway.
Juice- Juice is on Team B and Tsubaki Factory is on Team A. The only thing left is the Sapporo show the day after tomorrow.
This year's concert of Halo! Project concert, I hope you will enjoy the way the groups mix and mingle with each other.
Tsubaki Factory's new album, 3rd Moment, was released today.
This album includes new live songs, songs written especially for this album, and the graduation song sung by the graduating members on their last stage,
This album is filled with songs that only Tsubaki can produce, so please listen to it.
On April 10, Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2023 Autumn! Atara yo! Riko Yamagishi and Yume Kishimoto's graduation special Akatsuki video will be released.
Please be sure to get it to enjoy the very quiet, chic, and mature world of Tsubaki Factory.
On March 10, the 7th anniversary of Tsubaki Factory's major debut, Live Realize, will be held at the Ichikawa City Cultural Hall.
We are looking forward to seeing you all at the event, which we are sure will be a surprise to everyone who comes to the venue.
JuiceJuice Concert Tour 2024 Manline will start on April 20 at Harmony Hall Zama.
This will be the last spring tour since Akari Yumemaru is scheduled to graduate. This will be the last time we will tour with our current group, and I hope many people will be able to see JuiceJuice as it is now.
Let's have a lot of fun!
Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2024 Spring Come on!
This will be the last spring tour with 12 members, and I hope we can absorb a lot of things from Ms. Shinnuma and make this tour to grow up even more.
The Carmon Neutral 2024 by Satoyama Umi Movement will be held at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31.
I look forward to this event every year and hope that many people will come.
Hello! Ste is a channel where the members of Hello! Project will appear more and more.
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
This time we have Yume Kudo from JuiceJuice and Marin Fukuda from Tsubaki Factory.
Bye!
Thank you for watching!